Previously on "Power"...
When we met,
what'd you think I was gonna be?
The biggest goddamn drug
dealer in New York City.
I don't know any old,
wrinkled drug dealers.
They're either dead or inside.
Since when do you lie to me?
Since when do you hide shit?
Ghost took back his loyalty,
so now it's time
for you to do the same.
I want to change my life for you.
I don't want
to break up your marriage.
You like having me around, huh?
- I do.
- I want your offer.
- $6 million to own it outright.
- Truth is not for sale.
The moment I detect disloyalty,
I cut it out.
You was right about Rolla.
- I'm sorry it turned out like this, G.
- It was Kanan, right?
You were still tight
after all these years.
I am your friend.
Rolla's dead.
You owe me money.
And you owe me bodies.
You make sure my son
ain't there when you do it, neither.
I want Ghost dead
before I get out.
I'm your friend.
I guess we should get to it.
I am your friend.
They say we supposed
to get 10 inches.
Ripped By mstoll
I'm your friend.
Glass was empty.
The coroner found whiskey
in Rolla's stomach.
So whoever killed him
gave him a last drink.
That's classy.
So I hear you turned down
the new border task force in Detroit.
- Guess you'll be sticking around?
- Rolla's murder is a new lead.
Sure, but we have
no money to follow it.
With Lobos
being prosecuted in California,
they've shut us down.
Now Rolla's death
is officially an NYPD case,
just like Anibal.
Might be the same hitter.
I don't think so.
He had a drink.
At the kill shot, he fell right out
of his chair onto the floor.
No defensive wounds,
no sign of struggle.
- You think it was someone he knew.
- And he didn't see it coming.
He trusted the person.
You think it was the distributor?
You think it was Ghost?
You could be right.
But it doesn't matter.
Cali will have Lobos indicted
by the end of the week.